When are you going on your next trip?
你下一次出差是什么时候?
Pretty soon.It'll be to the Czech Republic.
快了. 是去捷克共和国(Czech Republic).
Oh,I'm dying to go to Central Europe.
Oh, 我太想去中欧(Central Europe)了.
I'm looking forward to it,
我盼着这次旅行快点儿到来,
but it will be so much work.
但会有许多工作要做.
Why?
为什么?
Jim Bigelow wants the company's hotel in Prague to develope marketing plan just like ours.
Jim Bigelow想要公司在Prague的饭店制定出一个和我们一样的市场营销计划.
Wow,great!
Wow, 太棒了!
In three months.
要在三个月内完成.
That is a lot of work.
那有好多工作要做.
Anne,if I can do anything to help,
Anne, 要是我能帮上什么忙,
please let me know.
请让我知道.
I will.
我会的.
And next time,take me with you.
下一次带我一起去,
I want to sit in a cafe in the Old Town Square.
我想到Old Town Square的咖啡馆里坐坐.
That is my favorite thing to do.
那也是我最喜欢做的事.
And I hear there's great jazz.
我听说那儿的爵士乐很棒.
Oh yes.
And serious shopping.Crystal...
也是购物的好地方.水晶…
I'll pick some up for you,if you like.
我会帮你买一些, 如果你喜欢.
Antique glass...Embroidery...
古董玻璃器(Antique glass...)...刺绣(Embroidery)...
I've seen lovely china from there.
我还看过很漂亮的瓷器, 来自那边.
Nina,it'll be much easier if you just come along.
Nina, 要不你和我一起去吧,那样事情就简单多了.